Register of the Young Americans for Freedom records
Hoover Institution Archives
- Subject File, 1961-2003
  - Ban the Soviets Coalition, undated (Box-folder 78: 2)
  - California Republican Youth Caucus, 1984 (Box-folder 78: 3)
  - Charles Edison Youth Fund, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 78: 4)
  - Christian Coalition on Campus, 1987 (Box-folder 78: 5)
  - Citizens for Reagan, 1982 (Box-folder 78: 6)
  - Cultural Laureate Foundation, Inc., 1972-1976 (Box-folder 78: 7)
  - Goldwater, Barry, 1970 (Box-folder 78: 8)
  - Independent Student Newspaper Association, 1973 (Box-folder 78: 9)
  - Leadership Initiative, 1967-1994 (Box-folder 78: 10)
  - Legal Affairs Council, 1990 (Box-folder 78: 11)
  - Lukens for Senator, 1970 (Box-folder 78: 12)
  - National Center for Public Policy Research, undated (Box-folder 78: 13)
  - National Review, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 78: 14)
  - National Youth Alliance, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 78: 15)
  - Nixon-Agnew Campaign, 1968 (Box-folder 78: 16)
  - Penn State YAF, 1992-1994 (Box-folder 79: 1)
  - Reagan, Ronald, 1970-1987 (Box-folder 79: 2)
  - Stop National Student Association, 1970 (Box-folder 79: 3)
  - Student Action Council, 1970-1987 (Box-folder 79: 4)
  - Student Committee for Victory in Vietnam, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 79: 5)
  - Third Party, 1983-1986 (Box-folder 79: 6)
  - Voluntary Military, 1970 (Box-folder 79: 7)
  - White House, 1970 (Box-folder 79: 8)
  - World Anti-Communist League, 1972 (Box-folder 80: 1)
  - World Youth Crusade for Freedom, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 80: 2)
  - Young America's Campaign Committee, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 80: 3)
  - YAF and the Reagan Administration, 1981 (Box-folder 80: 4)
  - YAF Foundation, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 80: 5)
  - Young Conservatives National Council to Repeal the Draft, 1973 (Box-folder 80: 6)
  - Young Republicans, 1973 (Box-folder 80: 7)
  - Youth Against McGovern, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 80: 8)
  - Youth for Buckley, 1961 (Box-folder 80: 9)
  - Youth for Voluntary Prayer Amendment, undated (Box-folder 80: 10)
  - 1974-1992 (Box-folder 80: 11)